Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Alumni Files, 1876-
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Alumni Files, 1876-
- Series II. 1900-1999
  - 1990-1999
    - Hoisington, Cynthia E., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 68)
    - Huber, Mark G., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 69)
    - Hunter, Suzanne Lynn, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 70)
    - Jameson Jordan, Karolina Antonia, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 71)
    - Jones, Michael Sean, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 72)
    - Kauffman, Rebecca M., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 73)
    - Kaufman, Alison B., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 74)
    - Kenyon, Stacy M., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 75)
    - Kramer, Marc H., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 76)
    - Liu, Christine S., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 77)
    - McCracken, Jeanette L., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 78)
    - Minnier, Stacie M. L., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 79)
    - Murray, Melissa L., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 80)
    - Norris, Moria L., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 81)
    - Ognibene, Eve R., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 82)
    - O'Leary, Heather J., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 83)
    - Paccione, Nicole R., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 84)
    - Pasnik, David J., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 85)
    - Price, Rebecca A., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 86)
    - Ranjithan, Bharathi A., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 87)
    - Reetz, Christopher T., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 88)
    - Rockwell, David A., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 89)
    - Ritter, Kimberly A., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 90)
    - Robinson, Sara Walton, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 91)
    - Scala, Kristen A., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 92)
    - Scheck, Bonny J., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 93)
    - Schein, Amy H., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 94)
    - Schlaefler, Marlene, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 95)
    - Scuderi, Katrina, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 96)
    - Seacord, Rebecca Erin, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 97)
    - Seaman, Jeffrey A., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 98)
    - Sickles, Sharon A., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 99)
    - Silverstein, Shana C., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 100)
    - Simpkins, Natacha, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 101)
    - Smith, Daniel M., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 102)
    - Sparks, Tara L., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 103)
    - Storey, Ryan T., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 104)
    - Teague, George Scott, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 105)
    - Tornusciolo, Dawn Zezule, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 106)
    - Voronin, Gregory O., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 107)
    - Wagner, Karin A., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 108)
    - Walker, Jennifer Ayn, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 109)
    - Warren, Joy P., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 110)
    - Weingardt, Keith R., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 111)
    - Weinkle, Tristan K., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 112)
    - Weinmann, Dale S., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 113)
    - Weisner, Chris Edward, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 114)
    - Wilson, Karin C., 1999 (Box 29, Folder 115)
    - Wilson, Sarah Elise, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 116)
- 2000-2011
  - 2000-2011
    - Capel, Katrina, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 117)
    - Capel, Michael, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 118)
      1960-2009
    - Osborn, Kenneth C., 2001 (Box 29, Folder 119)
      1983-2014
    - Park, Ed, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 120)
    - Klene, Erin, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 121)
    - Osborn, Kasey, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 122)
    - Chediak, Jennifer, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 123)
    - Lynn, Amy, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 124)
    - Barnard-Whitford, Adrienne Elizabeth, 2011 (Box 29, Folder 125)